





Lead consultant seeking roles in Robotic Process Automation, Software Development, Application Programming, Blue prism development, Ui path, Network Administration, Incident Management, BMC Remedy, WinSCP, GITHUB, Jira, Citrix XenApp, XenDesktop



Total Experience: 8 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Highest Degree: MCA[Computers]

Current Designation: Lead consultant
Current Company: Wipro Technologies

Current Location: Hyderabad / Secunderabad

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Chennai, Hyderabad Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Team Lead/Tech Lead

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Key Skills: Lead consultant, Team Lead/Tech Lead, Robotic Process Automation, Software Development, Application Programming, Web Development, Requirement Gathering, Network Administration, Blueprism, Ui path, BMC Remedy, WinSCP, GITHUB, Jira, Citrix XenApp, XenDeskto

Verified : L Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 19-Jan-21 Last Modified: 19-Jan-21

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Summary

8+ years of overall BFSI experience in IT Industry which includes Digital transformation (Robotics Process Automation - Blueprism/Ul path), Citrix, Virtualization Project/Team management (Agile), Design, Development and Production support. Currently working as a Lead consultant in Wipro Technologies, Bangalore since May 2018.

Certified developer in UiPath and Blueprism

Having nearly 4 Years' Experience in Robotic Process Automation Blue Prism Tool UiPath.

4+ years of experience in Citrix XenApp and XenDesktop Lead administrator.

Analyze client processes, identify automation opportunities, define Robotic Process Automation value proposition, Re-engineer process to improve automation potential and recommend RPA(UI Path/Automation Anywhere/Blue prism) approach/strategy.

Involved in process automation collaborations with business users globally to analyze business processes, recommend RPAbased solutions for the processes using Automation Anywhere and UI path studio and Blue prism.

Work Experience

- Wipro Technologies as Lead consultant May 2018 to Till Date
- Centurylink as Sr. Technical Lead Feb 2016 to May 2018
- HP Enterprise as Delivery consultant Apr 2015 to Feb 2016

^ Back to Top

Education

PG: MCA (Computers) from Sri Venkateshwara University in 2011

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name Version Last Used Experience

Blue Prism 4.0 & 5 & UI Path

Wedows Hoor V



Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

vviнuows. пурет-v	
Java, SQL	
BMC Remedy, WinSCP, GITHUB, Jira	
Windows servers 2012,2016	
Citrix XenApp, XenDesktop, VMware, VDI	

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQs - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.